http://pathways.org/privacy-policy/

Order
Find resources for your baby's development:
Select Age Range
355 E Erie St. • Chicago, IL 60611 • (800) 955-2445
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Thank you for visiting www.pathways.org, www.pathwaysawareness.org, www.pathwayscenter.org, www.inclusioninworship.org, or www.team-w.org. Pathways Foundation (“Pathways.org”), which includes Pathways Awareness, Pathways Center, Pathways Inclusion in Worship, and TEAM W respects the privacy of online visitors and donors. This Privacy Policy explains our collection and treatment of any personal information you may provide to us through this site.
Collection of Personal Information
You may visit this site without providing us with any personally identifiable information. You may choose to submit personally identifiable information in certain circumstances, such as when you join the mailing lists for Pathways.org newsletters and other mailings; purchase an item online from Pathways.org; make an online contribution to Pathways.org; or register for access to certain pages on this site. In these instances, we may ask you to provide information, including your name, address, and other similar contact information.
We may also ask you to create a username and password to access certain restricted pages on this site. Where we ask for personally identifiable information on this site, we may not be able to process your request or provide you with access to restricted pages if you decide to withhold any of the information we request.
Personal Information From Children
We do not knowingly collect, disclose, or use personally identifiable information provided by a minor under the age of 13. If you learn that your child has provided personally identifiable information to Pathways.org, please contact us and we shall remove that information from our lists.
Use of Personal Information
We may provide your personally identifiable information to contracted vendors that assist Pathways.org with mailings and online sales transactions.
Pathways.org does not sell or otherwise share with organizations who are not our partners any of the personally identifiable information received on this site. Pathways.org may use personally identifiable information for Pathways.org-specific direct mailings, such as email updates, newsletters, and solicitation and advocacy letters, and we may share your information with organizations and companies that partner with us to provide information, products, and services that we believe are of real value to the community we serve. If you do not wish for us to share your information with our partners, please let us know by contacting us at the email address below, and we will gladly respect your decision to “opt-out” of receiving communications from Pathways.org and/or its partners.
Pathways.org may also share with third-parties aggregate information regarding online visitors. Aggregate information identifies overall visitor activity, but does not provide information on any individual user.
Internet Information Security
Pathways.org takes reasonable precautions to ensure that any personally identifiable information
you provide on this site is kept confidential and stored in a secure environment, and that only those personnel with legitimate business purposes will have access to this information. Even so, we cannot guarantee that data provided to us will not be subject to loss, alteration, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or destruction. It is important to be aware that all internet transmissions are subject to security breaches and errors. You should take precautions in choosing the information you send to Pathways.org via email and safeguard any passwords or special types of identification you use to access this site.
International Notice
Personal information that is voluntarily submitted to Pathways.org online, via electronic communication, or otherwise, such as through email listservs, may be maintained or accessed in servers or files located in the United States under United States privacy laws, which the European Union has not deemed to provide “adequate” privacy protection. If you do not consent to having your information processed and stored in the United States, please do not provide it.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data that a website may transmit to your browser. The cookie may be stored on your computer to identify your computer when you return to the site, but does not identify you as an individual user. Pathways.org uses “session only” cookies to track your use of this site that do not retain your personal information.
Changes to Your Personal Information
We strive to ensure the accuracy of any personal information you provide to us online. If you would like to update or review the personal information we have on file for you, please email your request to friends@pathways.org. To assist us in properly updating our files, please include your old and new personal information in your request.
Effective Date
This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 2, 2014. Pathways.org reserves the right to change or modify this policy as needed. Your continued use of this site signifies your assent to any modifications of this Privacy Policy. By visiting this site, you indicate your assent to Pathways.org’s Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
Pathways.org 150 N. Michigan, Suite 2100
Chicago, Illinois 60601
Phone: 312-893-6620
E-mail: friends@pathways.org
MEDICAL INFORMATION DISCLAIMER
The information on this website is not intended to be, nor is it, medical advice on the management or care of sensory, communication and motor delays. Our goal is to provide information that is helpful, accurate, and current, but knowledge in the field of developmental medicine is growing rapidly and all data are subject to change without notice. Neither Pathways.org nor any parties who supply information to this system make any warranty concerning the accuracy of any information found on or exchanged through this system. No endorsements of any products which appear on this website are given or implied by Pathways.org.
Pathways.org does not endorse any specific medical regime. You should not change your medical schedules or activities based on the information provided at this site. Always consult
with a doctor, healthcare provider, or other medical professional before making any medical decisions.
Please note that Pathways.org does not employ medical personnel in their national office. If you have a specific medical question, please contact your physician.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES, LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, AND INDEMNIFICATION
The information provided here is for informational, educational and entertainment purposes only. It is not intended to replace, and should not be interpreted or relied upon as, medical or professional advice. Your use of this site means that you agree to the terms and conditions detailed in our disclaimer.
YOUR USE OF THIS WEB SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. BY NAVIGATING THIS WEBSITE, YOU WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS RELATING TO THE USAGE OF MATERIAL OR INFORMATION SUPPLIED BY PATHWAYS.ORG. PATHWAYS.ORG AND PARTIES INVOLVED IN DEVELOPING, PRODUCING, OR DELIVERING THIS SITE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE OR INJURY OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THIS SITE. PATHWAYS.ORG AND THE AFOREMENTIONED PARTIES ALSO SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE OR INJURY RESULTING FROM ANY OMISSIONS OR ERRORS IN THE CONTENT OF THIS SITE OR FROM YOUR RELIANCE ON INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM THIS SITE. IF YOU RELY ON THIS WEBSITE OR ANY INFORMATION, PRODUCT OR SERVICE AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT THERE MAY BE DELAYS, OMISSIONS, INTERRUPTIONS, INACCURACIES, AND/OR OTHER PROBLEMS WITH THE INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES PUBLISHED ON OR PROMOTED OVER THIS SITE. THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU “AS IS.” PATHWAYS.ORG, ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS, VENDORS AND LICENSORS CANNOT AND DO NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS, CURRENTNESS, NONINFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OF THE ADVICE, OPINIONS, STATEMENTS OR OTHER INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE (OR ANY INFORMATION, GOODS OR SERVICES THAT ARE REFERRED TO, ADVERTISED OR PROMOTED ON, OR SOLD THROUGH THIS WEBSITE). PATHWAYS.ORG, ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS, VENDORS AND LICENSORS DO NOT GUARANTEE THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE ERROR FREE, OR CONTINUOUSLY AVAILABLE, OR THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL PATHWAYS.ORG OR ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS, VENDORS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY DAMAGES OTHER THAN DIRECT DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE LINKED TO FROM OR ADVERTISED OR PROMOTED ON THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, OR OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (INCLUDING LOST REVENUES OR PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR LOSS OF DATA), EVEN IF WE ARE ADVISED BEFOREHAND OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SOME OF THESE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS PATHWAYS.ORG, ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS, VENDORS AND LICENSORS, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, OWNERS AND REPRESENTATIVES AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, OF WHATEVER NATURE, THAT ARISE OUT OF ANY BREACH BY YOU OF THIS AGREEMENT OR YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE.
JURISDICTION
This site is intended for access and use solely by residents of the United States and subject to all applicable laws of the United States, and in particular, the State of Illinois. Use of this site implies and is subject to the consent to the laws of the United States and the jurisdiction of the courts of Illinois.
RESERVATION OF RIGHTS
Pathways.org reserves the right to alter or delete material from this site at any time without notice. Please check often for updates, as we reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify these Terms of Use at any time, and your use of the site indicates your acceptance of any revisions to these terms.
DISPUTE RESOLUTION
Visitors must contact Pathways.org to resolve any disputes that arise from use of this site.
Back to Top Arrow
Back totop
